gazaro.com 2009-05-05

# Gazaro Privacy Statement

By using Gazaro.com or Gazaro.ca, you agree to the collection and limited use of your personal information as described in this policy. If we make any significant changes to this policy, we will post a notice of such changes on the login page to keep you informed.

## Summary

  * We will never spam you or give your personal information to anyone.
  * You control when and how we send messages to you.
  * You can delete your account at any time.

## How we treat your information

### We will never spam you.

We send you weekly notifications of great deals, but you can turn these off.

### You control when and how we send messages to you.

You control the types of deals you receive, how often you receive them, and the mediums (e.g. email, RSS, SMS, etc) that we send notifications on.

### You have full control over your information, including the ability to delete your account.

You can change your account information and preferences at any time.

You can delete your account, permanently wiping any of your data from our system. For a period of time after account deletion, your account data may remain in our archive files or in our cache but will eventually be completely purged.

If we make any significant changes to this policy, we will notify you by posting a notice of such changes.

### We will safeguard your personal information and use it only to deliver you the best service.

Our algorithms will use your location and the products, brands, and stores you specify to discover the best deals on the things you want.

Gazaro support staff may review your personal information if you request us to do so as part of a support call, where it is required by law, and to maintain or diagnose issues with our system.

We may transfer information about you if Gazaro is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Gazaro will notify you by email or put a prominent notice on the Gazaro website that your information may be transferred and subject to a different privacy policy.

### We may sell, rent, or share information about user habits in aggregate only.

We will never compromise your privacy. We will never intentionally disclose information, unless required by law, that could is individually identifiable.

## The information we collect

  * **Personal information:** Your name, email address, password, and region (zip/postal) code 

All passwords are stored using 1-way encryption algorithms so we can’t see your current password. If you lose your password, we will generate a new one and send it to you.

  * **Shopping information:** The products, brands, and stores you like 

Our algorithms use this information to figure out the best deals on the product you want from the brands and stores you like.

  * **Site usage:** Logins, activity, votes, and error logs 

This data is used to monitor Gazaro’s health and to diagnose issues when they arise.

## Cookies and log files

Gazaro sends a "cookie" to your computer that contains an identification number that is unique to the computer you are using. We use this cookie to provide you with a seamless experience, and so that we can record how our service is being used.

As is done with most web sites, we log each visit to each web page. A log entry can contain information typically found in the "header" of your web browser's request such as the browser type you used, your Internet Protocol address, and the date and time of day. We may also log your cookie's identification number and the URL of the last site you visited. This log information is important for security, audit, quality improvement, as well as for monitoring the health of our service.
